agencyplatform.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Agency Platform

At Agency Platform, we understand the trust our users place in us and we fulfill our responsibility to protect the privacy of our users. Any website collecting information about users is legally required to inform users of how information is treated. 

**Information you provide:**

In order to use our services you must first create an account with Agency platform. During the creation of an account you will be required to share certain basic information such as username, company name, company logo and email address. You will also be required to create a password for the account created with Agencyplatform. Any additional data provided will be an optional field and it would be up to you whether or not to share that information. 

We do not store sensitive information like credit cards in our database or anywhere on our servers. For payments we use secure third party payment gateways like Google Checkout, Paypal and CCavenue. 

**Access:**

For certain services like Google analytics and Google webmaster tools we use both login and API access to get data in to our platform. This information is collected to provide services only. However in future we will switch our access to API access only so that we won't require to store client login details in our database. Whenever that plan is implemented it will be informed on our privacy policy page. For other services like Facebook, Twitter we use API access only to get information in to our platform. For such services we don't require login details to fetch data. 

**Storage:**

Agencyplatform stores information as long as it is necessary to provide services to you or sometimes longer for the purpose of research. If there comes a point when the information is longer necessary then we either delete the data or anonymize the information and merge it with other data to help in our research so we can provide better service and application functionality to you. The access to such data is not accessible to any third party vendor and but only to authorized personal only. 

**Google Analytics** : **Agencyplatform does not collect and store privately identifiable information from Google Analytics. Nor do we correlate data from Google Analytics with personally identifiable information.**

**Agencyplatform calls and gets data from Google Analytics and represents the data in our Agencyplatform. As soon as you remove access from Google Analytics module then all data related to Google Analytics is deleted at the same time.**

**Security:**

We have a good setup of security in order to prevent any unauthorized access to the data.These include internal audits of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store data. 

We restrict access to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Services:**

When an account is created you don't get access to all the services of Agencyplatform. The services will be provided based on the plan/package signed up with us. 

**Cookies**

When you visit Agencyplatform then we may store one or more cookies on your computer. Agencyplatform uses session ID cookies for the purpose of login. 

**Notification of Changes:**

Should there be any changes in our policy, it will be published on our privacy page. 

**Third Party Applications:**

In order to have better experience Agencyplatform may use third party applications in certain modules. The information collected by third party application is governed by their privacy policies. The information collected by agencyplatform through third party application is processed under this privacy policy. 

**User Communication:**

For any queries, or help requested to us by either email, phone or contact us form then we will retain those communications in order to process inquiries. For matters or questions asked to agencyplatform we will respond to them either by email or phone. We may use your email to inform you about our services. 

**Contact Information:**

If there are any questions or queries regarding our privacy policy then please contact us at support@agencyplatform.com .
